https://www.acmehe.com/privacy-policy/

800-888-5267 CLICK TO CALL info@acmehe.com
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ACME Home Elevator collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.acmehe.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ACME Home Elevator. PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. WEB BROWSER COOKIES Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. HOW WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION ACME Home Elevator may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes: – To improve customer service     Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. – To personalize user experience     We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. – To improve our Site     We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY ACME Home Elevator has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. CONTACTING US If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.   This document was last updated on August 22, 2012
800-888-5267 Contractor’s State License Number: CA #521967 Acme Home Elevator serves all of California including: Anaheim, Beverly Hills, Berkeley, Irvine, Long Beach,  Los Angeles, Newport Beach, Oakland, Sacramento, San Bernadino, San Diego, San Francisco, San Jose, Santa Ana, and Walnut Creek  Privacy Policy For Remarketing
